(忆往昔)
死人血对吸血鬼来说是致命的
Dead man's blood is posion to vampires.
大多关于吸血鬼的传言都是鬼扯
Most Vampires'lore is crap.
杀死他们的唯一方法
The only way to kill them.
就是砍头
Is by beheading.
嘿 Dean 我是Jody Mills
Hey,Dean,Jody Mills.
Jody 你确定
Jody,Are you sure.
你准备好回来面对这些东西了吗
You are ready to jump back in the fray.
这些鬼东西一直不肯放过我
This wackodoo stuff keeps coming.
我了解他们越多 就越有能力对抗
More I know,better armed I 'll be.
你是不是也
Did you get.
重生了一次吗
Born again.
是的
Yeah.
我可不做我信守不了的承诺
I don't make promises I can't keep.
我很享受去教堂
I enjoy church.
经过了发生在我儿子和丈夫身上的那些事
I mean after my son and my husband.
我需要一些对我来说有意义的东西
I needed something that made sense to me.
(如今)
好了 小姐 冷静点
All right,Missy,calm down.
放我走
Let me go.
冷静
Calm down.
让我出去
Let me out.
Frank 有人砸碎了前门玻璃
Hey,Frank,someone smashed the front window.
在达尔文五金店
Over at Dawson's Hardware.
有可能是入室抢劫
Possible B&E.
需要你去看看
Need you to check it out.
收到 可是犯人候审间这里还有人
Yeah,copy that,but bullpen isn't empty.
这有我拘留的人
I got someone to hold in.
警长正赶去警局
Sheriff is heading to the station now.
很快就会到
They won't be alone long.
收到 我马上过去
Roger that.I'm heading out.
嘿 别丢下我一个人
Hey,don't leave me.
求你了
Please.
Cody
Cody.
原来你在这啊
There you are,girl.
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me.
拜托
Come on.
非要问出来吗
You don't really need to ask that,do you.
其他人和你在一起吗
Are the others with you.
大家都去猎食的时候
Everyone was off on a hunt when.
我发现你逃跑了
I realized you'd run away.
我决定帮你和他们一个忙
Figured I'd do you and them a favor.
在他们发现你跑了之前
And come take cared of this.
过来把这事处理了
Before they even know we are gone.
你不能进来抓我的
You can't get me in here.
警察们都忙着查我伪造的入室抢劫
Cops sure was in a hurry to check that B&E I faked.
根本没看到我进来
Barely even saw me coming.
我一直都跟你说
I keep telling you.
你可以逃跑 可以藏起来 但是
You can run and you can hide,but.
我们最终都会找到你
We will always find you.
你们俩可真养眼啊
You boys are a sight.
Jody
Jody.
你肩膀怎么样了
How's the shoulder.
只在下雨天才会疼
Only aches when it rains.
你们俩最近如何
How you boys been.
- 还不错 - 随时准备逃命
- Peachy - Touch and go.
我懂那种感觉
I know the feeling.
好吧 你给我们准备了什么
So,what you got for us.
这是个吸血鬼 没错
Yeah,that's a vamp,all right.
是吗 Sammy
I don't know,Sammy.
看起来Jody不再需要我们的帮助了
Looks like Jody might not need our help anymore.
是啊 娃娃们都长大了 对吧
Oh,they grow up too fast,don't they.
玩笑随便开
Yeah,joke all you want.
但是这些东西的老窝里还有更多
There's more where this came from.
更多
More.
我的手下昨晚抓住了一个逃跑的
My man brought in a runaway last night.
她身上没有身份证
There's no ID on her.
事实上 什么也没有
Nothing on her,actually.
除了一张离开内布拉斯加州的车票
Except for a bus ticket out of Nebraska.
不明身份的极致
Total Jane Doe.
她甚至不肯说自己的名字
She won't even give me her name.
这姑娘简直就是野兽
The girl basically feral.
毫无教养
She's got zero manners.
我救了她的命 连句谢谢也不说
She didn't even thank me for saving her.
这位兄台
Anyhow,this thing.
为了接近她可是费了一番力气
Went to plenty of trouble to get at her.
从他的话语里听出
And to hear him tell it.
其他人跟他一样都想要她
The others will want her at least as bad as he did.
- 听起来像是个吸血鬼窝 - 嗯
- Sounds like a nest - Yeah.
吸血鬼窝
Nest.
我猜这地方一定
I'm guessing that.
没有听起来那么温暖舒适
Isn't half as cute and cozy as it sounds.
恐怕你说的没错
Oh I'm afraid not.
Wilson和Fisher
Wilson and Fisher.
你俩要是FBI 我就是Taylor Swift
You two FBI,then I'm Taylor Swift.
你们不是取我牙齿证明
That wasn't a dental ID.
你们在查我有没有獠牙
It was a fang check.
你们是猎人
You are hunters.
要知道 你还活着
And you are alive.
是因为警长经过猎人的特训
Because hunters trained the sheriff.
我想你应该先说句谢谢
The first word out of your mouth shoud be a thank you.
你到底和吸血鬼是什么关系
So who were you to these vamps,anyway.
你到底有什么特殊之处
What's so special about you.
你们的老窝在哪
Is there a nest.
抱歉打扰
Sorry to interrupt.
找到和她吻合的DNA了
Got a match of her DNA.
Annie Jones
Annie Jones.
报告上说她06年在卡诺什被诱拐
Reported abducted outside Kanosh 06'
是被祖父母抚养长大的
Raised by an elderly grandparents.
没有其他活着的亲人了
No living kins.
你们觉得当年是吸血鬼把她掳走了吗
You think the vamps are the ones took her.
跟吸血鬼同居8年可够久的
Eight years is long time for human live with vampires.
还不被杀死或者同化似的
Without getting killed or turned.
你们俩是专家
You are the experts.
但是看那个吸血鬼跟她交谈的方式
But there was something familier.
好像他们很相熟
About the way this vamp talked to her.
Jody说的没错
Jody is right.
她这里有条伤疤 吸血鬼吸食留下的伤疤
And she had scars on the,feeding scars.
伤痕都分层了
They are layered.
就像是历经数年留下的
As if they've been built on for years.
这么说她是个吸血鬼奴隶
So she is a bloodslave.
我们以前见过
We've seen it before.
吸血鬼把人类当做宠物 或者活的饲料库圈养
Vampires keeping people as pets,human feedbags.
有时候这些人
Sometimes these slaves.
对他们的主人非常忠诚
Stay loyal to the captors.
- 没错 - 是的
- Yeah - Right.
你指
So this girl's not talking cause.
这女孩不肯说是因为
She's got a case of what.
是因为吸血鬼斯德哥尔摩综合症吗
Vampiric Stockholm syndrom.
她在保护老窝
She's protecting the nest.
你感到愧疚
So you feel a debt.
他们给你地方住 养育你
They gave you a home,raised you.
Annie 我们懂
Annie,we get it.
忠诚是一种强大的武器
Loyalty is a very powerful thing.
- 我叫Alex - 不 这不是你名字
- My name is Alex - No,it's not.
你的真名是Annie Jones
Your name is Annie Jones.
吸血鬼把你偷走了
Those vampires stole you.
他们是怪物Annie
They are monsters Annie.
Alex
Alex.
他们根本不爱你
They didn't love you.
只爱你的血
They loved your blood.
你是他们的食物
They fed on you.
是我喂他们
I fed them.
我愿意
My choice.
他们是我同胞 我饿了他们给我吃的
My brothers,they brought me food when I was hungry.
他们猎食失败的时候
So when they struck out on a hunt.
我喂饱他们
I fed them.
他们是我家人
They are my family.
好吧 你很在乎他们
Ok,you care about them.
但是 Alex
But,Alex.
你不会无缘无故离家出走
There's a reason you decided to run away.
是时候
It was time.
是时候离开他们 靠我自己活下去
To move on and get along on my own.
那你有没有想过
And how do you think.
他们是不会乖乖接受你逃跑的事实的
That decision is gonna sit with the rest of the nest.
已经有人找到你了
One of them already pursued you.
你以为 当其他人发现你逃跑了
You think when the rest of them find out that you left.
他们就会放过你 会善罢甘休吗
They're just gonna shrug and cut their losses.
你和他们一起生活了那么多年
You lived with them for years.
他们尝过你的血
They've tasted your blood.
对你的气味知根知底
They've had your scent down cold.
你能逃多远
I mean how far can you run.
躲多久
And for how long.
你根本没考虑过 对吗
You didn't think this out,did you.
你的行为
What would happen.
会伤害到其他人
Who might get hurt.
例如 你哥哥
Your brother,for one.
他叫Cody
His name's Cody.
是她杀了他
And she killed him.
那是因为你做出的选择
Because of the choice you've made.
有因必有果
These are the consequence.
你有两个选择
You've got two options.
他们 还是你自己
Them or you.
我们能保护你的安全 我们能帮你
And we can help you,we can keep you safe.
同时你也得帮我们
But you have to help us.
老窝在哪儿
Where's the nest.
我不能
I can't.
妈妈知道我逃跑了
After what's happened.
一定会找到我 然后杀了我
Mama finds me,she'll kill me.
Mills 没事吧
Mills,you okay.
难怪她没谢我
No wonder she didn't thank me.
那怪胎是她哥哥
The creep was her brother.
我没事
I'm fine.
那什么 其实我只是
You know,mostly,I'm just.
其实我在想她的名字
I'm hung up on the name.
Alex和Annie明明很像了
Alex and Annie,they are so close already.
为什么还要改名
Why'd they change it.
从她的车票可知
Okay,so we know from her ticket.
Alex从内布拉斯加州的奥尼尔
That Alex hopped a bus.
上了一辆客车 对吧
Out of O'Neill,Nebraska,right.
- 嗯对 - 显然
- Mm-hmm - Obviously.
如果能追踪到具体地点更好
It'd be better to go in with a firm location.
不过镇子也不大
But the town ain't that big.
没有洞穴或者其他野外的藏身地点
There are no caves or other natural hiding places.
那我们就去查个遍
All right,so go in,canvass it cold.
我做了一张表归纳了
Well,I work together a short list.
可能的老窝所在地
Of possible nest locations.
有一家闲置的消防站
There's an empty fire station.
还有四五家没人的房子
Four or five derelict homes.
一天就能查完
Nothing we couldn't hit in a day.
好
Okay.
你确定
Are you sure you are all right.
一个人能看住她吗
To babysit her by yourself.
虽然女孩喜欢开溜
Oh,well,girls are flight risk.
也不算友好
Not exactly friendly.
我应该应付的过来
But I think I can handle baby-sitting detail.
这个警局已经暴露了
The station's been made.
你最好去避一避风头
It might be worth heading upwind for a while.
吸血鬼擅长跟踪
Vamps are trakers.
- 好极了 - 嗯
- Terrific - Yeah.
我在郊外有一所小木屋
I've got an old family cabine outside of town.
- 可以住那儿 - 嗯
- That'll work - Okay.
失踪一天
Shouldn't raise too many eyebrows.
大概没人会在意的
Me being gone for a day.
希望如此 你确定不要我们帮忙
Maybe,but sure you don't want backup.
你想让我为了躲避吸血鬼的追踪
You want me to enlist my men in a.
去惊动我的手下
Protection detail against vampires.
Frank还不知道昨晚袭击的真相
Frank's in the dark about what hit him last night.
他看行尸走肉
The guy still his nightmares.
晚上都能做恶梦
About the barn episode of Walking Dead.
他们都是好警察
They are good cops.
接受不了这些
They are not ready for this.
Jody 你以前查资料的时候
Jody,at your late night reading.
有没有遇到过死人血这种东西
Did you ever come across anything about dead man's blood.
吸血鬼一粘马上就能晕过去
It takes vamps down like a horse tranq.
这东西好 我要备点
I would not say no to some of that.
不是说我有多想用
I mean,not that I'll need it.
倒是你们要去找他们的老窝
You guys're gonna jump on these vamps.
然后在他们意识到自己家里人不见了之前
And be back here before they even realise.
安全回来 对吧
Their kin's missing,right.
又不是我的错
Well,it's not my fault.
Ralph今天没上班
Ralph didn't show up for work today.
我只能连上两班了
I had to pull a double shift.
马上到家
I'll be home soon.
Conner你吓死我了
Conner,you scared the.
对不起 我不应该跟踪你
I'm sorry I shouldn't have snuck up on you like that.
只是 你最近有看见Alex吗
It's just,you haven't seen Alex around,have you.
你妹妹啊
Your sister.
我没见
No,I can't say I have.
抱歉
Sorry.
所以说卖给她车票的不是你
Huh,so you didn't sell her the bus-ticket outa town.
你在问我有没有帮你那个自闭症的妹妹
Did I help your shut-in kid sister get away from her.
从她那个怪胎窝里离家出走呢
Weird scary-ass squatter family.
没有
Answer's still no.
你的意思是Ralph撒谎
So you're saying Ralph lied to us.
他可是说
Cause he said.
是你卖票给我妹妹的
That you sold her a ticket.
之后我们就结果了他
Right before we killed him.
你竟敢说我们家是怪胎窝
You calling my family weird.
让你见见什么叫怪胎
Oh honey you have no idea.
怎么
What.
对你来说太土了吗
Too rustic for your taste.
这里有我太多美好的回忆
Oh,I've a lot of great memories.
我小时候常常和家人来这里
Used to come up here all the time first as a kid.
后来和我的
With my parents and then with my.
来吧 里面可比在外面看舒服多了
Anyhow,it's a lot nicer than it looks from the outside.
提醒你一下 这片树林
FYI,the woods around here.
不熟悉的人进去
Really easy to get lost.
是很容易走丢的
If you don't know your way around.
我可是对这片林子了如指掌
Me,I know it like the back of my hand.
懂了 我不会试图逃走
I got it,don't try running.
逃不了多远
You won't get far.
你知道那些东西没用对吧
You know this doesn't work right.
对吸血鬼无效
On vampires,it's useless.
那不是用来对付吸血鬼的
It's not why I have it.
你家人吗
This is your family.
对
Yes.
他们人呢
Where are they.
哦 死了
Oh,dead.
你刚那句话 能说得很礼貌
You know,there are about a thousand more polite ways.
的方法多了去了
That you could say that.
考虑到你是一群怪物养大的
I will give you a pass.
就不和你计较了
On account of the whole raised-by-monsters thing.
他们怎么死的
How did they die.
惨死
Horribly.
你一定累坏了
You must be exhaust.
我知道你昨晚一宿没睡
I know for a fact you didn't sleep last night.
我没事
I'm fine.
别客气 我给你铺个床
It's no problem,I can make up a bed.
说了没事
I'm fine.
随便你
Suit yourself.
这地方被法院抵押了 对吧
This place is a foreclosure,right.
对
Yep,it is.
和其他几间一样
Just like the rest of them.
有人在这儿呆过
Well,somebody's squatting here.
窗户被糊上了
Blackout windows.
喂
Hey.
喂 要搭把手吗
Hey,you need a hand with that.
看来用不着了
I guess not.
集体外出狩猎
You go out with the family.
把美味的食物带回来
Bring home a nice dinner.
可为什么是你负责洗碗
How did you get stuck doing the dishes.
每个人都有自己的角色
We all have our roles to play.
你的任务就是毁尸灭迹 对吧
Yours being destroying the evidence,yeah.
干得不错
Nice job.
Ralph Hedges和Stacy Kepler
Ralph Hedges Stacy Kepler.
为什么选他俩
Any reason you targeted them.
因为 饿了
Yeah.Hunger.
你那帮亲友呢
And,so,the family's what.
出去餐后散步了
Out taking a nice after-dinner stroll.
我相信他们很快就回来了
Oh,I'm sure they'll be back real soon.
你没听清我的问题
What I asked was.
他们在哪
Where are they.
笔不错
Nice shiner.
有什么能帮你们的
Can I help you all with something.
说实在的
As a matter of fact.
我们正用得上你
I think you can.
你不说是吧
You don't want to talk.
我也没什么损失
No skin off my back.
你瞧 吸血鬼吸人血 碎人尸
Cause you see,a blood-sucking,body-chipping vamp.
已经丧尽天良了 但你们
That's bad enough,but vamps.
还绑架儿童
That kidnap kids.
我很乐意你送走
Well,I'm going to enjoy putting you down.
你说的没错
Of course.
我早知道 又是Alexis
Oh,I knew this was about Alexis.
我警告过妈妈
I warned mama.
那女孩早晚会坏事的
That girl would screw everything up for us one day.
妈妈
Mama.
是那个把你们变成吸血鬼的人
As in one vamp turned you all.
除了我们的小妹妹
Well,all of us but little sis.
她 神圣不可侵犯
She was,uh,too good to turn.
不管我们怎么说 妈妈就是下不了手
Mama couldn't bring herself to,no matter what we said.
不管Alexis怎么捣乱
No matter how bad Alexis got.
捣乱
Bad.
我猜猜
Let me guess.
你没有未成年的小妹
You never had a teenage sister.
碍手碍脚
Dragging her heels.
无时不刻不在抱怨
Whining,near constant,about everything.
越来越看不惯我们吸人血
But more and more about the blood.
就好像她自己很高尚一样
Like she's somehow above it.
高人一等
Like she's better than us.
就因为她不用吸人血
Cause she don't feed on people.
她就是比你强 蠢货
She is better than you,dumbass.
她总是很忧郁
Her moping.
青春期大爆发良心不安什么的
That teenage crisis of conscience crap.
虽然我们也很烦 但是小孩儿就爱作
It's annoying as hell,but it's just an act.
真到了紧要关头
When the chips are down.
她还是会站在我们这边的
She'll always choose us over humans.
你以为我们是怎么
I mean,how do you think.
长久以来避开你们的追踪的
We stayed off your radar all these years.
像她那样年轻漂亮的迷途羔羊
Pretty,young,lost-looking thing like her.
让人无法抗拒
Irresistible.
特别是那种死了都没人知道的
Especially to the kind of man few people would miss.
我们打猎有时候 只是为了活动筋骨
I mean,sure,we hunt sometimes for sport.
但是送上门来的 更容易
But it's a lot easier and a lot.
也更安全
Safer to get delivery.
拜托 甜心
Oh,come on sweetie.
不想告诉我名字吗
Aren't you gonna give me a name.
我叫Ann
It's Ann.
小甜心
Sweet Ann.
你知道
You've got any idea.
我要对你做什么吗
What I am about to do to you.
我知道
Yeah,I do.
你什么也做不了
Nothing.
这是个聚会什么的吗
Is this a party.
她是你的诱饵
She's your lure.
吸血鬼们一生的追求
Best a vamp could ask for.
你最好相信我
And you better believe you.
别太沉迷了
Don't get that good at it.
除非你很享受
Unless you enjoy it.
把你迷得团团转
In her own sweet way.
女人就像吸血鬼一样嗜血
Girl's as bloodthirsty as any vampire.
Jody
Jody.
Alex?Alex
Alex?Alex.
Alex
Alex.
放松
Easy.
抱歉
Sorry.
我给你做了三明治
I made you a sandwich.
想吃的话就在外面
It's out there if you want it.
警长
Sheriff.
我祖母她怎样
My grandma.
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
不 没关系 毕竟那么多年了
No,it's fine,it's been years and.
她也年纪大了
She was old.
明白了 谢谢
You got it.thank you.
她没接电话
She's not answering.
我刚从本地警局查到受害者名字
I just ran the victims'names through local P.D.
他们俩都在O'Neill汽车站工作
They both work at the O'Neill bus station.
所以他们杀了那俩人是为了Alex的地址
So they killed them for Alex's location.
- Jody - Dean,什么事
- Jody - Dean,what's up.
听我说
Listen to me.
那群吸血鬼已经知道Alex
The vamps knew that Alex.
去苏福尔斯了
Went to Sioux Falls,okay.
他们可能已经过去了
They're probably already there.
我们马上上路去找你们
We're on our way there next.
还有件事
But there's something else.
关于Alex的
There's something about Alex.
等一下
It can wait.
- 他们来了 - 什么
- They are here - What.
现在就在这儿
At the cabin now.
- 我们马上过来 - 快
- We are on the way - Hurry.
她挂了
She hung up.
- 走吗 - 对 在外面等我
- We moving? - Yeah,meet you outside.
Alex
Alex.
Alex 快 我们该走了
Alex,come on!We gotta go.
Jody
Jody.
我们该走了
We gotta go.
Jody
Jody.
Alex
Alex.
Jody 快救救我
Jody!Help.
放手
Let me go.
快走
Come on!Let's go.
走
Move it.
Jody
Jody.
嘿 你还好吗
Hey!Are you okay.
Alex去哪儿了
Where's Alex.
我们以为你知道
You tell us.
我追出来想阻止他们
They came and I tried to stop them.
但是你被打晕了
And you got knocked out.
这种事很正常
Well,happens to the best of us.
你还活着算幸运了
Just lucky you're alive.
你说他们回去过了吗
You think they went back to the nest.
肯定已经回去过了
Of course they did,why wouldn't they.
现在问题是 他们看到死了一个同伙
Question is what they're gonna do.
会怎么办
If they find the brother dead.
- 那我们就杀回去 - 好
- So we go back now - Okay.
我跟你们去
I'm coming.
Jody 那个
Jody?Hey.
等一下 你受伤了
Hold on.You're hurt.
我们跟你们去
I'm coming.
Jody 我们两个就可以端了他们的老窝
Jody,we can handle a nest on our own.
我才不管他们住什么地方
I don't give a fig about the nest.
- 那个女孩儿本来在我的保护之下 - 是
- That girl was under my protection - Okay.
但是她不可信
That girl can't be trusted.
她是个诱饵
She is a lure.
她只是一步棋
She's a...honey trap.
是她一直给吸血鬼提供食物源的
She's been feeding people to those vamps.
我不在乎 不管她做了什么
I don't care.Whatever she did.
一定都是被他们逼的
She did because they made her.
这还能有理了
Oh,that's a reason.
- 她是个孩子 - 对
- She's a kid - Yeah.
一个从话都说不清楚开始
A kid who's been playing vampire murder.
就跟吸血鬼一起杀人的孩子
Since before she was in braces.
Jody 我哥说得没错
Jody,he's right.
最好的情况 也不过
Our best,her loyalities are.
- 她不可信 - 而且你怎么知道
- Screwed - And how do you.
她到底想不想被救
Even know she wants to be saved.
过去的8年里
For the past 8 years.
她一直在为整个巢穴猎食
She's been baiting hook for the entire nest.
她手上的鲜血比我们杀过的
She's got more blood on her hands.
怪物的血都多
Than most monsters we killed.
你是说她上了你们黑名单吗
Are you saying she's on your list.
- 没有 我们没这么说 - 目前没有
- No,we are not saying that - Well,not yet.
听着 她是很可怜
Look,it sucks,okay.
但是
It does.
我们那么多年猎魔的经历告诉我们事实有多残酷
But we hunting monsters comes harsh truth.
这次是清除行动
This is a clean-up mission.
不是营救行动
It's not a rescue.
你想想这些都是为什么
What is this even really about.
你都不了解她
You barely know the girl.
我跟你们去
I'm coming.
如果你们谁
And if either one of you lay.
敢动Alex
So much as a hand on Alex.
先得过我这关
You had to go through me.
你在Conner手里还真是拼死挣扎啊
Put up a quite struggle with Conner.
他说你差点儿把他眼睛挖出来
Said you nearly took his eyes out.
也有可能
Maybe that was just.
是他把你打晕的借口
His excuse for knocking you out.
你都不知道你闯了多大的祸
You have any idea the mess you've made.
我们不在的时候 两个猎人血洗了这里
Hunters raided the place while we were out.
折磨拷问之后 又杀了Dale
Tortured and killed Dale.
我们的巢穴暴露了
Our home has been made.
又要重新找家了
We're gonna have to move again.
- 妈妈 我不是故意 - 嘘嘘嘘
- Mama,I never meant - Shhhh.
我们会处理好的
We will all find our way.
虽然一切都乱了套
Things got screwy.
但最重要的是你回来了
But you're back now.
什么
What.
我还以为
After everything I thought you were.
你以为什么
You thought what.
我会打你
That I'd hurt you.
还是会杀你
Kill you.
我永远都不会伤害你的
I would never hurt you.
我的乖宝宝 我的乖Alex
Not my baby girl,not my sweet Alex.
你怎么能那么想
How could you even think that.
宝宝 你为什么这么做
Baby,why did you do it.
为什么要跑
Why did you run from us.
妈妈我爱你
I love you,mama.
真的 我只是
I do.I just.
我承受不住了
I couldn't take it anymore.
鲜血
The blood.
死亡
And the death.
那些人的尖叫
The sounds of their screams.I just.
我继续不下去了
I can't do it anymore.
每次完事之后
The way I feel afterwards.
那种愧疚
The guilt.
我宁死也不要经历那些
I'd rather die than feel that way again.
都是我的错啊
It's my fault.
- 什么 - 这一切
- What - All of it.
都是我的错
It's my fault.
我早就该转化你
I should've turned you years ago.
卡车都在车道上
Their truck's in the driveway.
我们就直接走过去
So we're walking right into it.
- 以前有比这更糟的 - 对
- We've faced worse odds - Yeah.
Jody
Jody.
这是突袭
This is a raid.
不要太感情用事
So tread lightly stay close.
主要是毁了他们的老窝
Priority is clearing the nest.
Alex是次要 懂了吗
Alex comes second,you got it.
嗯
Got it.
我真是太自私了
It was so selfish.
想亲眼看着你一点一点长大 所以我没转化你
I want to watch you grow up I kept putting it off.
你还看不出来吗
Don't you see.
那些你经历的感受
These things you've been feeling.
所有的愧疚 所有的苦楚
All the guilt and suffering.
都是人类的情感
Those are human feelings.
现在还不算晚
It ain't too late.
我可以带走苦痛
I can take the pain away.
然后我们就可以永远在一起
And then we can stay together.
我们一家人
As an family.
就像这一切都没发生过
Like none of this ever happened.
你觉得呢
Would you like that.
扔了
Drop it.
Alex 来
Alex,come on.
过来 我们走
Come on honey.We gotta go.
- 走开 - 我们得快走
- Go away - We gotta go.
他们对你做了什么
What did they do to you.
抱歉 Jody
I'm sorry,Jody.
我已经做了选择
I made my choice.
她选了我
She chose me.
别想
No,no,no.
想想一回到家看到
Hell of a sight to come home to.
自己兄弟
Brother.
死在地上
Lying dead on the floor.
还真不知道是Winchester家的人干的
No idea it was a Winchester that had done it.
所以
So.
谁下的手
Which one of you was it.
是谁
Which one of you.
砍下我兄弟的头
Took off my brother's head.
是你
Was it you.
还是他
Was it him.
还挺合适
Pretty fitting.
一手换一足
Brother for a brother.
这栋房子是个好家
This place has been a good home to us.
但是你们既然毁了这儿
But since you two had to come around and ruin it.
我们又得上路
We're gonna have to hit the road.
找新家
And find a new one.
等我们走的时候
And when we hit the road.
我们喜欢装好午饭
We'd like to pack a lunch.
还真是有备而来啊
Can't say you didn't come prepared.
Alex
Alex.
别烦我女儿
Hey,don't be bothering my girl.
她正在经历一个阶段
She's going through something.
一个过程
A process.
你对她做了什么
What did you do to her.
给她喝了我的血而已
Fed her my blood.
现在她正自己转化中
She's on her way now.
只剩下进食即可
All that's left is to feed.
求你了妈妈
Please,mama.
放她走
Let her go.
我已经喝了你的血了
I already drank from you.
放她走
Let her go.
还给我女儿留了个好印象
Made an impression on my girl,I see.
宝宝 这是你人类的那一半在说话
Baby,this is the human half of you talking.
过了这阵之后
After the change.
这个人类 对你来说什么都不是
This human,she ain't nothing to you.
话说警长啊 你有心理问题
Clearly,Sheriff,you got issues.
你的生活中缺了一块儿
Some hole in your life.
拿我的Alex来填充
You're using my Alex to fill.
要是平时 我会说
I would say.
好好过你的日子去 但是
Go and get a family of your own,but.
你也知道
Well,you know.
这话从你嘴里说出来还真是可笑
That's pretty rich coming from the woman.
Alex不是你偷来的吗
Who stole Alex to begin with.
我养着她
I have fed her.
供她衣食
Clothed her.
9年来无时无刻不爱着她
Loved her going on nine years.
我觉得母爱只有血亲才给得起吗
You think motherhood's just about blood.
你根本不懂什么是母爱
You don't know the first thing about it.
也许我是不懂
Maybe not.
但是我知道什么不是母爱
But I know what it isn't.
当她成为你的负担的时候
And it ain't about forcing her to be.
强迫她变成你就不是母爱
Like you the second she becomes inconvenient.
看到她的伎俩了吗
Don't you see what she is trying to do.
这个贱人想让你背叛我
This hunter cop bitch is trying to.
这样自己就有活路了
Turn you against me to save her own hide.
她说的话一个字儿都不能信
Don't believe a word she says.
她不是你母亲
She ain't your mother.
这桶差不多了
Tapped this keg.
准备抽那个短头发的
Get the short hear one ready.
该做个了结了
Time to finish this.
Alex
Alex.
是她的名字吗
Was that her name.
你以别人名字给她取的名
You named her after someone.
是你女儿吗
Was it your daughter.
我一直不明白为什么要改名字
I couldn't figure out why you changed her name.
开始还以为你对自己偷来的感到难为情
I thought maybe you were ashamed of your theft.
但是你根本没有羞耻心
But you have no shame.
你说我用她填补生活中的空缺
You said I was using her to fill a hole in my life.
对 我是这样的
And you're right,I am.
你也是
You are,too.
妈妈
Mama.
果然同类最了解同类
I guess it takes one to know one.
那个Alex
That Alex.
死了很久了
She died a long time ago.
但心还是会痛
And it still hurts.
你还能感觉到缺失的苦痛
You still feel it,the loss,the pain.
就像一块儿挪不动的石头
Like a stone in your gut.
只有她在身边的时候
It hurts just a little bit less.
才会痛得少一点
Whenever she's near.
你个贱人
You bitch.
看着我
Look at me.
看着我 混蛋
Look at me,bitch.
- Dean - 我知道
- Dean - Yeah,I know.
你不会为我做同样的事
You wouldn't have done the same for me.
Jody还在
Jody.
好消息 女警官
Good news,lady cop.
不管你失去的是谁
Whoever you lost.
你们很快就要团聚了
You're gonna see them again.
非常快
Real soon.
Alex
Alex.
你怎么能
How could you.
你是我女儿啊
You are my girl.
对不起 妈妈
I'm sorry,mama.
亲爱的 别看
Don't watch this,sweetheart.
刚才干得漂亮
Nice work back there.
尤其那句 看着我混蛋
Look at me,bitch.
你有什么想挖苦讽刺的
Hey,you got another snappy one-liners.
我洗耳恭听
I'm all ears.
我只想说
What I'm saying is.
在我看来似乎你很享受
It looked to me like you were enjoying it.
可能 有点儿过了
Maybe too much.
所以呢
And.
哦 抱歉 我没反应
Sorry for not putting on the hair shirt.
杀那些该杀的怪物
Killing things that need killing.
是我们的工作
Is kind of our job.
从中获取愉悦
Last I checked,taking pleasure in.
不算犯罪
That is not a crime.
没错 可是
Right but.
警局里怎么样了
How's things back at the station.
Frank被打惨了
They beat Frank up pretty bad.
不过还好能喘气
But at least they left him alive.
他一直不停的道歉
He kept apologizing for spilling.
他说漏嘴那件事
The beans about the cabin,but.
我说那是我的问题
Told him that one's on me.
说到道歉
Speaking of apologies.
我们很抱歉
We own you a big one.
是我们误会了那个女孩
We were wrong about the girl.
不 对于我 你们说的很对
No you were right about me.
我失去了判断力
My judgement was clouded.
而且 这个案子
You know, working this case,it brought.
带回来那些感受
Feelings back.
这些年我一直麻痹的感受
Feelings I've been trying to bury for years.
用工作 宗教
You know,buried it under work and religion.
甚至用约会
Even dating.
结果我们都知道
We know how that worked out.
但是
But you know.
那感觉还是在那 最深处
It's still there,underneath.
悲伤
The grief.
我也不知道到底是
Don't know what that means.
怎么回事 我就是
For me just that I've been.
我骗自己能忽略这种感受
I've been fooling myself think I could ignore it.
不管怎样 谢谢你们
Anyway,thank you.
谢谢你们来
For coming out.
谢谢你们治Alex
For curing Alex.
你不需要谢我们
You don't need to thank us.
你才是解救她的人
You're the one who killed her sire.
这样她就有初源的血
Got her blood.
确定管用吗
Sure it'll work.
就我个人经验来说
Well,speaking from experience.
这几天会过的很辛苦
It'll be a rough of couple of days,but.
她必须克服
She should pull through.
你确定不想我们留下帮你吗
Are you sure you don't want us to stay.
我一个人能行
I am good.
事情结束之后
After it's done.
她该怎么办
You know what to do with her.
别我一来你就起来
Don't get up on account of me.
好热
I am hot.
要不要
Should I grab a.
过会儿就又冷了
I'll just be cold again in a second.
估计是治疗的一部分
It's part of the cure,I guess.
要吃点东西吗
You want something to eat.
不了 反正都会吐
No I'll just throw up.
不过 谢谢
But...thank you.
我想让你知道
I want you to know that.
当提出来的时候 我只是
When mama offered...I just.
我不想又一次让她失望
I couldn't dispoint her again.
我应该惭愧到这辈子都抬不起头
I had enough to be ashamed of as it is.
Jody 我做了一些错事
Jody I have done things.
你无需解释
You don't have to explain.
我知道
I know.
无论你想从我这里得到什么 我都会给你
Whatever you want from me I'll give it.
如果你想 我就在你身边
If you want,I'm here.
你经历的那些事
What you've been through.
尤其是过去的两天
The last 48 alone.
你的家人
Your entire family.
所有你认识的 你爱过的
Everything you've ever known or loved.
没人能理解你
No one can understand that.
你可以
You can